University of Connecticut, Health Center Records 1997.0129
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series V: School of Dental Medicine, undated, 1969-1995
  - Endodontics Annual Report, Oral Radiology Annual Report, Oral Biology Annual Report, Oral Diagnosis Annual Report, Behavioral Sciences & Community Health Annual Report, Oral & Maxillofacial Surgery Annual Report, 1969-1988 (Box 94)
  - Orthodontics Annual Report, Periodontics Annual Report, Pediatrics Annual Report, Restorative Dentistry Annual Report, Graduate Dental Education Annual Report, Continuing Education Annual Report, 1969-1988 (Box 95)
  - Dental School Catalogs, 1968-1987 (Box 96)
  - "Compass" and Dean Robinson retirement annoucement, 2002, 2005 (Box 129)
- Series VI: Dempsey Hospital, undated, 1921, 1955-1992
  - McCook Hospital: Policies, Reports, Manuals, History, Medical Board Minutes, Tumor Registry, Annual Report, McCook Cancer Report, Hartford Public Health Survey, 1955, 1967-1983 (Box 97)
  - Hospital Annual Report, Hospital Support Services, Hospital Policy Manual, Nursing Rounds, Nursing recruitment Brochure, Dept. of Nursing Services Annual Report, Dept. of Nursing Services Annual Report, 1972-1993 (Box 98)
  - UCONN Health System, Publications: Dempsey Dateline, "Hospital Housestaff Manual," Housestaff Photographs and Rosters, Dedication, AIDS Info, Results of the Integrated Diagnostic Work Sys. Analysis E.C. Murphy Ltd., Annual Reports, Employee Student Health, Nursing, Post-anesthesia Care, OR, Medical records, Rehabilitation, Hospital Planning, 1973-1995 (Box 99)
  - Dempsey Hospital: Annual report, Family Practice and Medical Group, Volunteer Office Annual Reports, "Reimbursement RX", "Pharmacy Newsletter", "Pharmacy Therapeutics Letter", "Pharmacy & Therapeutic News", Pharmacy Dept. Annual Reports, Professional Advisory Committees, JCAHO Accreditation Survey, 1969-1998 (Box 100)
  - Appraisal Municipal Hospital & Almshouse, Capital Area Health Consortium v.I-III, 1921, 1977 (Box 101)
  - Clinical Affairs/JDH Annual report, 2005 (Box 129)
  - JDH--4CI (Coll.Ctr.for Clin Care Improve), 2005 (Box 129)
- Series VII: Library, undated, 1960-1997
  - MLAA (Medical Library Assistance Act), CDMSL (Council of Developing Medical School Libraries), McCook Hospital Library Collection, Copyright Law, Lyman Maynard Stowe Exhibit, AHEC, Security Ins. Co. - Rental Agreements, 1969-1973 (Box 102)
  - Planning for Medical Library, Gifts to Library, Director Sam Hitt's Correspondence, CRMP (Connecticut Regional Medical program), 1960-1970 (Box 103)
  - CRMP, 1970-1976 (Box 104)
  - CRMP, 1970-1976 (Box 124a)
  - CRMP, 1968-1975 (Box 125)
  - CRMP, 1967-1974 (Box 126)
  - CRMP, 1968-1973 (Box 127)
  - Floor Plans, Plans for Moving Library to Farmington, Stowe Library Plans for Furnishings, Library History, Pictures, Public Services, Book Sale, Director Jim Morgan Correspondence, Council Minutes, Jacob Sharp's Donation, Markle Foundation, Library Committee Meetings, Library Audiotape & Slide Tour, Library Organization Chart, 1968-1988 (Box 105)
  - Library Newsletter/Update, News for Health Sciences Librarians in CT/RI, Information Services Department: Grants Bibl., Seminars/Workshops, Library Guides, Automation Newsletter, Automation Plans, Bookplates, NLM Grants, 1974-1997 (Box 106)
  - NLM Regional Medical Library Programs, NN/LM Document Delivery Manual, NN/LM Sounding Line, 1965-1997 (Box 107)
  - Library Annual Report, Journal Holdings Lists, 1965-1986 (Box 108)
  - Journal Holdings Lists, undated (Box 109)
  - UCHC/YML Periodical List, AV Resource catalog, HSAVRL (Health Sciences AV Resource List), CNAVRL (Comprehensive Nursing AV Resource List), undated (Box 110)
  - UCHC AV List, New Acquisitions, 1971-1987 (Box 111)
  - Dedication, Arcari retirement, Update, Alumni News, 2005 (Box 129)
  - EFTS Quarterly Fall 04-Fall 05, 2004-2005 (Box 129)
  - Project Manual proposal, 2002 (Box 129)
- Series VIII: Biomedical Communications Department, undated
  - (Contact staff member for information on photographic materials from this department)
  - Biomedical Communications Department, Connecticut Non-print Resources Lists, 1970s (Box 112)
- Series IX: Students, undated, 1968-1996
  - "The Handbook", Dental Student Handbook, "The Newspaper", Dental Student Affairs Newsletter, Medical Student Affairs Newsletter, "ConnUs", Student Association, Honor Code, Committee Against Racism, UCONN Professional, Student Rosters and Photographs, Student Resource Book; "NoStat", "The UConn Professional", 1974-1998 (Box 113)
- Series X: Pharmacy, undated, 1972-1991
  - Connecticut Poison Control Center annual report, papers and brochures, Drug Information Service Policy and Procedure Manual, annual report, 1975-1991 (Box 114)
- Series XI: Faculty Collections, undated, 1968-
  - Minutes of the General Faculty Meeting, The University of Connecticut's Health Center--an Examination of its Development, Current Operation and Future Possibilities for the Commission for Higher Education, Medical and Dental Staffs faculty lists, Urban Development Committee Hearings, transcripts of sessions, deals with litigation regarding the construction of the Health Center, 1968-1974 (Box 115)
  - Patterson Papers (Box 116-118)
  - Hinz Papers (Box 119-122)
  - Oral History Tapes and transcripts and description of dedication. Interviews by: Whitney Jacobs, Director, Public Affairs, UCHC. [Transferred to Center for Oral History Interviews], 1983-1988 (Box 123)
    - John Alsop, [no transcript], 5/21/86
    - Homer Babbidge, 28 pp., 11/18/83
    - Howard Bailit, 45 pp., 4/27/85
    - Jack Blechner, [no transcript], 1/19/85
    - Francis Braceland, 10 pp., 10/19/84
    - Charles Burstone, 21 pp., 5/8/85
    - Robert Cairns, 7 pp., 8/22/84
    - Cosmo Castaldi, [no transcript, 2 tapes], 11/14/84
    - Jane Chapaitis, 25 pp., 1/23/85
    - Sherwin Cooperstein, 31 pp., 10/24/84
    - James Cullen, 10 pp., 4/15/85
    - Lester Cutler, [no transcript], 3/27/85
    - John Dempsey, 13 pp., 7/25/84
    - John DiBiaggio, 18 pp., 1/2/85
    - Kevin Dowling, [no transcript], 10/18/88
    - Thomas Draper, 11 pp., 1/31/85
    - William Fleeson, 22 pp., 8/14/84
    - Stephen A. Flis, [no transcript], 8/17/88
    - Franklin Foote, [no transcript], 7/18/84
    - Lewis Fox - Interview #1, 25 pp., 3/1/84
    - Lewis Fox - Interview #2, [no transcript], (2/25/85
    - Eli Freedman, [no transcript], 12/16/84
    - Edward Gant, 18 pp., 5/25/85
    - Clair Gardner, 8 pp., 2/19/85
    - Isidore Geeter, 16 pp., 11/17/84
    - Irving Goldschneider, 29 pp., 4/10/85
    - Edward Hanna, [no transcript], 12/26/84
    - Ira Hiscock, 6 pp., 2/17/85
    - John Ives, 15 pp., 2/24/85
    - Charles Jerge, 22 pp., 2/21/85
    - Anthony Keller, 16 pp., [transcript only], 1/30/85
    - Marion & Richard Keller, 7 pp., 8/8/84
    - Vincent Kling, 17 pp., 2/18/85
    - 
    - 
    - 
    - 
    - 
    - 
    - 
    - 
    - 
- Series XII: 2012 Addition, 2002; 2012; 1.0 Linear feet
  - Administrative records, ephemera, optical disks, 2002; 2012; 1.0 Linear feet Ordered as recieved (Box 2012.0035_1)
    Scope and Content Note
    Subjects include: Liaison Committee on Medical Education (LCME), School of Medicine.